It’s not always what you expect…
A Perfect Ending is a drama, romance film directed by Nicole Conn.
This intimate drama follows Rebecca, a woman who has kept her sexuality a
secret from her friends but chooses to reveal it to a stranger.
While Rebecca's revelations may not yield the results she
expects, a perfect ending is still in reach.
Rebecca Westridge, played by Barbara Niven.
Paris, played by Jessica Clark.
Mason Westridge, played by John Heard.
Valentina, played by Morgan Fairchild.
Jessica Westridge, played by Kerry Knuppe.
Kelly, played by Imelda Corcoran.
A Perfect Ending is a film written and directed by Nicole Conn.
The film explores themes of female homosexuality, lgbt, woman director, lesbian.
The tone is emotional.